<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CustomWidgets</string>

    <string name="err_items_count_title">Wrong number of XML strings</string>
    <string name="err_items_count_message">Numbers of XML string resources for Activities\' names and
    corresponded descriptions are not match.</string>
    <string name="err_items_count_btn">Close</string>

    <string name="item_btn_launch">Launch</string>




    <string name="activity_oval_touchable_view_title">OvalTouchableView demonstration</string>
    <string name="activity_oval_touchable_view_description">The white containers are the FrameLayouts with background color #FFFFFF which contains OvalTouchableViews with MUCH_PARENT params.
    circular/oval shapes are the &lt;shape-drawable/&gt; backgrounds of the OvalTouchableViews which honor the "pressed" and "selected" states.
    Touchable areas of the OvalTouchableViews match background shapes\' areas.</string>


    <string-array name="children_activity_names">
        <item>OvalTouchableViewActivity</item>
        <item>IdifjdsNsudfhsd</item>
        <item>Okfsdlf</item>
        <item>Jiosdfhosdf</item>
        <item>adsufhds</item>
        <item>Lasdjkf</item>
        <item>Odskflnslf</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="children_activity_description">
        <item>Demonstrates CircleTouchableView widget which provides a View with oval touchable area.
        If the view is square, the touchable area is round. Touching outside the touchable area will be
        ignored bu the widget. state-list background with oval shapes as items is suitable for this widget.</item>
        <item>sldkfjds fkjsdfjsldjfsid fijf wejf weijf iwe fjjwehf jkhefkjhe kjhwej kfhjkewh jkwefhjweflk  wewjefjew jwekhkjwe fjwehfwherf89 we fw8e fw8ehf84h fhiowehf iwhef hfh4u iwehfkjwen cfkjwen fc  cwecwfgreg erg </item>
        <item>dddd f f f  gdfkjhg fdsjhsdjk hfsdoi ufhs iudohf  f dfhasdfu hef he fh ef h edhfjasd fasdjf hjasdf agdqwgdy qwgy  gweqyw ed879f g89 98fdg fdj ogisdhfw 8rf h sdhfisdhfoiewh iwehf iweoh ohsd fsdihf sidhfs89dfh sdhc sdhcs iodhco isdhco</item>
        <item>wefriwe foiwej wijf lkgklfgk[ rktg e[g kpprkf wpekf wmf.wemf lkwejf we ew iweoj fwejf weofj weprojfwe9iry8 y48 84y r8 w0fu e-qw9fu pwe9uf jwoeifhwep f wep fjwepjf wejf wepojf</item>
        <item>doi qjdiqjw diqhe dfoieqwhj fiwehf 8we hfwe8fyh weoihfwe ohfwehf9w0e fwe-0jf epq0jf pqhj fpoq9ewfh qp9fe  hpqoeh fpoqefu pjoqe fpoq jfpqefwef ergt qewdf iqoewdfoiqwe hdfoiqewhdfoiewq hfdioqw edfh qedfheqoi hfdoqiehfqf</item>
        <item>dfhasdfu hef he fh ef h edhfjasd fasdjf hjasdf agdqwgdy qwgy  g dfhasdfu hef he fh ef h edhfjasd fasdjf hjasdf agdqwgdy qwgy  g dfhasdfu hef he fh ef h edhfjasd fasdjf hjasdf agdqwgdy qwgy  g dfhasdfu hef he fh ef h edhfjasd fasdjf hjasdf agdqwgdy qwgy  g dfhasdfu hef he fh ef h edhfjasd fasdjf hjasdf agdqwgdy qwgy  g </item>
        <item>8fyh weoihfwe ohfwehf9w0e fwe-0jf epq0jf pqhj fpoq9ewfh qp9fe  hpqoeh fpoqefu pjoqe fp 8fyh weoihfwe ohfwehf9w0e fwe-0jf epq0jf pqhj fpoq9ewfh qp9fe  hpqoeh fpoqefu pjoqe fp 8fyh weoihfwe ohfwehf9w0e fwe-0jf epq0jf pqhj fpoq9ewfh qp9fe  hpqoeh fpoqefu pjoqe fp8fyh weoihfwe ohfwehf9w0e fwe-0jf epq0jf</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
